[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Don't move.
Friends.
Where are you two from?
Just passing through.
Who are you?
Just the two of you?
You look pale, brother.
That's a nasty wound.
Did something happen?
None of your business.
Kuan.
Sorry.
I need to take your temperature.
It's just routine procedure.
You're clear.
Don't be afraid.
We're out here...
to scavenge for supplies.
Our camp is just up there.
A fifteen-minute drive away.
Want to come back with us and rest up?
Thanks for the offer.
But no thanks.
I won't force you.
But if that wound isn't treated soon,
it'll definitely get infected.
He's right.
Your wound really needs to be tended to as soon as possible.
Then... sorry for the trouble.
We're here.
Dao is back!
We're back.
Open the gate! Dao is back!
Unload the goods, boys!
Sure thing, Dao.
What do you think?
This place used to be a film studio.
Everyone fled before the apocalypse.
We fixed it up and turned it into a base.
Dozens of people live here now.
- Both elderly and children. - Dao is back!
We all look out for one another.
Good work, Dao.
Good work.
Surprised?
We all used to work in film.
As for me, I used to be a producer.
- His name is Xiao Long. - Dao, you're back.
He used to be a stuntman.
Jiang is a prop master.
- Ms. Li, thanks for the hard work. - Hello, Dao.
Ms. Li used to be our costume designer.
Everyone has their own talents.
I didn't expect them to come in handy after the apocalypse.
Let me help you.
You're back. No need.
- It's quite heavy. - Thank you, Dao.
You're welcome.
I won!
Playing mahjong?
I'm done.
- Having fun? - Dao.
We just finished work.
We don't keep idlers here.
Those who can fight hunt and keep watch.
Those who are handy will cook and mend.
- Hello, Dao. - Hello.
That's our water storage area.
The water for laundry and cooking is all here.
We also have people who can't do heavy work.
They help raise the kids and grow vegetables.
We all have to survive.
This is the infirmary.
Hello, Dao.
Feeling better? Remember to change your dressing.
All right. Much better now.
Xiao Xi.
Remember to give this lad some anti-inflammatory medicine.
Okay.
You two can rest for a few days.
If you want to stay here long-term,
you have to work like everyone else.
After all, the resources here were accumulated little by little.
No one can stay here for free.
Thank you, Dao.
We'll just rest for two days.
We won't cause you any trouble.
Okay, no problem.
Xiao Xi.
Help me settle these two lads.
Check the storeroom
for any daily necessities they might need.
- This way, please. - Follow me.
Dou Dou, be careful not to fall.
That injury looks serious.
I'll have Dr. He from our base come take a look later.
No need to trouble him.
No, that wound needs to be cleaned and disinfected again.
Please bring some iodine and gauze later.
Sure. Tell Dao if you need anything.
Both of these rooms are empty.
Take your pick.
One room is enough.
One room it is, then.
I'll have someone bring over bedding and medicine shortly.
Okay, thank you.
[Apocalypse Log 14]
All done.
It's lights out.
Please return to your rooms.
Close your doors and windows.
Stay safe.
It's lights out.
Please return to your rooms.
Get some sleep.
Stay safe.
Good night.
Sleep here.
Then behave yourself.
Behave and go to sleep.
Sleep now.
- The weather is so nice today. - Lin Zai!
Grandma Qiu!
Child, you're alive!
Grandma...
What are you doing here?
Lie!
What happened to you two?
We all thought something had happened.
Grandma, it's a long story.
Lie and I did go to pick berries that day.
But we ran into some trouble on the way.
And then?
Then...
It's all thanks to Lie.
He protected me the whole way.
Grandma, how did you end up here?
Where are Chen Jin and Li Ming?
I've only been here for two or three days.
After you left, our camp was attacked by zombies.
Chen Jin and Li Ming protected me and we ran this way.
When we almost reached this camp,
we encountered a horde of zombies.
They hid me and lured the zombies away.
They never came back.
Later on, the people from this camp found me
and brought me back here.
Where did you get separated from them?
Not far from here.
An abandoned industrial area.
Let's borrow a car and look for them.
Don't worry, Grandma.
I'll bring them both back.
Be careful out there.
Come on, everyone, line up.
Thanks, man.
Help yourselves. Take as much as you need.
Come back if it's not enough.
Help yourselves. Come on.
You're just in time. It's dinner time.
Xiao Xi, get two trays for them.
Hey, no cutting in line.
Go to the back of the line.
No need. Dao, we're not here to eat.
I have something to ask you.
Go ahead.
Grandma Qiu, who just arrived, was from our camp.
She got separated from two others in the industrial area.
We want to go look for them.
The industrial area?
There are a lot of zombies there.
Are you sure you want to go?
We have to go, no matter how dangerous.
Yeah.
Tell you what.
I'll have Cheng and Kuan go with you.
They know that area better.
No need.
You're still injured.
Just lend us a car.
Just like that? "Lend us a car"?
We're not a charity here.
Dao, we're very capable.
I'm good at fixing electronics.
Lie can stand guard or search for supplies.
Please, lend us the car.
Thank you, Dao.
User's heart rate is consistently high.
Shut up, shut up!
Lie, was that you talking?
No.
Quick!
Doesn't look like there are zombies here.
What should we do?
There are quite a few of them.
Save your energy.
Li, rest in peace.
Lin Zai.